let MCQS = [{
    //Question 1
            question: "Who encouraged the world to ‘Get Down on It’ in 1981?",
    answer1: "Kool and the Gang",
    answer2: "Backstreet Boys",
    answer3: "One Direction",
    answer4: "Maroon Five",
    answer: 0
},

    //Question 2

            {
            question: "Who released the album 'Freedom' in the 00's",
    answer1: "Justin Bieber",
    answer2: "Katy Perry",
    answer3: "Shakira",
    answer4: "Akon",
    answer: 3
},
    //Question 3

            {
            question: "3 of the top 15 best-selling albums of the 00s belong to which 4-piece band?",
    answer1: "Coldplay",
    answer2: "Linkin Park",
    answer3: "Nirvana",
    answer4: "Backstreet Boys",
    answer: 0
},

    //Question 4

            {
            question: "'Who am I? Someone who's afraid to let go' who's lyrics are these?",
    answer1: "Marshmello",
    answer2: "XXXTentacion",
    answer3: "Lil-Wayne",
    answer4: "Logic",
    answer: 1
},

    //Question 5

            {
            question: "'So wake me up when it's all over' who's lyrics are these?",
    answer1: "Lil-Peep",
    answer2: "Avicii",
    answer3: "John Smith",
    answer4: "BTS",
    answer: 1
},

    //Question 6

    {
        question: "Where is it thought that the banjo originated?",
        answer1: "England",
        answer2: "New York",
        answer3: "Africa",
        answer4: "Colombia",
        answer: 2
    },

    //Question 7

    {
        question: "Which artist hit fame at a very young age",
        answer1: "Drake",
        answer2: "John Legend",
        answer3: "Avicii",
        answer4: "Justin Bieber",
        answer: 3
    },

    //Question 8

    {
        question: "Who released 'RAP GOD'?",
        answer1: "50 Cent",
        answer2: "Flipside",
        answer3: "Eminem",
        answer4: "Travis-Scott",
        answer: 2
    },

    //Question 9

    {
        question: "Which artists dated each other",
        answer1: "Justin and Selena",
        answer2: "Travis and Katy",
        answer3: "Beyonce and G-Eazy",
        answer4: "Shakira and Rixton",
        answer: 0
    },

    //Question 10

    {
        question: "Who released 'WAKA-WAKA'",
        answer1: "Shakira",
        answer2: "Akon",
        answer3: "Flo-Rida",
        answer4: "Sean Paul",
        answer: 0
    }
];